<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nicolas Blanco</title>
    <link>/authors/admin/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nicolas Blanco</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 18:25:23 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/authors/admin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>14 Amazing Facts about Polycategories and their Fibrations</title>
      <link>/post/polycategorical_clickbait/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 18:25:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/polycategorical_clickbait/</guid>
      <description>A quick compilation of facts about polycategories together with links to the appropriate litterature. Some are original work.
 Polycategories have been introduced by Szabo in 1975 in Polycategories. Polycategories are &amp;ldquo;categories with many-to-many morphisms&amp;rdquo;, i.e. polymaps have many inputs and many outputs. Polycategories correspond to classical Gentzen sequent calculus. Polycategories compose on one object. Composition of Polycategories is the cut rule. Representable Polycategories, a.k.a. two-tensor polycategories, are linearly distributive categories, see Weakly distributive categories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Classical linear logic via bifibrations of polycategories</title>
      <link>/talk/syco5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/syco5/</guid>
      <description>Linearly distributives categories correspond to polycategories bifibred over the terminal polycategory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 18:25:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>I am a PhD student in the Theoretical Computer Science group at the University of Birmingham. My supervisor is Noam Zeilberger.
My research interests include models of linear logic, categorical semantics of non-classical programming languages - e.g. probabilistic or quantum programming languages - and monoidal categories.
Before that I did a Master in Mathematical Logic and Foundation of Computer Science at the Paris Diderot University. During this period I did a five-month internship under the supervision of Benoît Valiron on the syntax and semantics of a linear probabilistic $\lambda\mu$-calculus.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>